[
 {
    "question": "Where was Fester lost in ?",
    "answer": "Bermuda Triangle"
 },
 {
    "question": "What is the real first name of Dr. Pinder-Schloss's son whom Tully recruits into pretending to be Uncle Fester and swindle the Addamses?",
    "answer": "Gordon"
 }
 {
    "question": "What game did the family play at the end of the movie, on Halloween?",
    "answer": "Wake the dead"
 },
 {
    "question": "Where did Gomez and Morticia meet?",
    "answer": "at a grave"
 }
 {
    "question": "What was Morticia's surprise for Gomez at the end of the movie?",
    "answer": "she's pregnant"
 },
 {
    "question": "what does Gomez call Morticia",
    "answer": "Cara mia"
 }
 {
    "question": "What did the judge give Gomez (in the courthouse)?",
    "answer": "a golf ball"
 },
 {
    "question": "Who owed Mrs. Craven money?",
    "answer": "Tully"
 }
 {
    "question": "How long has the 'Mamushka' been an Addams tradition?",
    "answer": "since God knows when"
 },
 {
    "question": "What does Morticia tell Wednesday to do at the breakfast table right before Mrs. Craven walks in?",
    "answer": "play with her food"
 }
]